<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Film - Tech - Hiking - Sport - Music</title>
    <description>My personal blog about my hobbies, interests and career</description>
    <link>https://iczster.github.io/</link>
    <atom:link href="https://iczster.github.io/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 11:21:53 +0000</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 11:21:53 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.10.0</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Nuremberg (2025) Film Review</title>
        <description>&lt;h2 id=&quot;-plot-summary&quot;&gt;📘 Plot Summary&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;p&gt;The film focuses on the true story of the psychological duel between US Army psychiatrist Douglas Kelley (Rami Malek) and the imprisoned Nazi leader Hermann Göring (Russell Crowe) during the first Nuremberg trial in 1945-1946. As the Allies attempt to hold the Nazi regime accountable for the Holocaust, Kelley works to understand the depths of their evil.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Despite arriving late and missing the first five or so minutes (or, let’s be honest, maybe twenty 😅), Nuremberg still pulled me straight into its world and held my attention all the way through its long, deliberate runtime.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;For...</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>https://iczster.github.io/nuremberg-film-review/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://iczster.github.io/nuremberg-film-review/</guid>
        
        <category>film</category>
        
        <category>review</category>
        
        <category>history</category>
        
        <category>drama</category>
        
        <category>Film</category>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Peter Hook and the Light Holmfirth Picturedrome</title>
        <description>&lt;h3 id=&quot;peter-hook-and-the-light--picturedrome-holmfirth--thursday-november-20th&quot;&gt;Peter Hook and The Light – Picturedrome, Holmfirth – Thursday, November 20th&lt;/h3&gt; &lt;p&gt;Thursday night at the Picturedrome in Holmfirth was a bittersweet celebration of post-punk classics as Peter Hook and The Light delivered a spellbinding performance. The crowd, buzzing with excitement, filled the intimate venue with energy from the moment Hooky and the band took the stage. Fans old and new swayed and sang along to every note, creating an electric and communal atmosphere.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;The setlist was a masterclass in nostalgia, opening with the punchy “Get Ready” followed by “Crystal” (New Order cover) and “60 Miles an Hour”, immediately...</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>https://iczster.github.io/peter-hook-holmfirth-picturedome/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://iczster.github.io/peter-hook-holmfirth-picturedome/</guid>
        
        <category>music</category>
        
        <category>gig</category>
        
        <category>review</category>
        
        <category>Music</category>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>CRASH Live 2025 A Retro Gaming Weekend in Warwickshire</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;CRASH Live 2025&lt;/strong&gt; event took place on the &lt;strong&gt;15th and 16th November 2025&lt;/strong&gt;, hosted at the Holiday Inn in Kenilworth, Warwickshire and what a weekend it turned out to be.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2 id=&quot;battling-the-storms-to-get-there&quot;&gt;Battling the Storms to Get There&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;p&gt;The journey down was &lt;em&gt;not&lt;/em&gt; for the faint-hearted.&lt;br /&gt; After a night of relentless storms, flooded roads, and detours that felt like bonus levels from a lost 8-bit adventure game, getting to the venue became an achievement in itself. But arriving at the hotel, greeted by fellow retro enthusiasts, made the effort instantly worthwhile. The banging breakfast went down well and it...</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>https://iczster.github.io/crash-live-2025/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://iczster.github.io/crash-live-2025/</guid>
        
        <category>retro</category>
        
        <category>gaming</category>
        
        <category>crash live</category>
        
        <category>events</category>
        
        <category>computing</category>
        
        <category>Tech</category>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Ingleton Falls Hike</title>
        <description>&lt;h2 id=&quot;ingleton-falls-hike-fierce-storm-waterfalls&quot;&gt;Ingleton Falls Hike (Fierce Storm Waterfalls)&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;p&gt;We tackled the always-awesome &lt;strong&gt;Ingleton Waterfalls Trail&lt;/strong&gt; just a day after &lt;strong&gt;Storm Claudia&lt;/strong&gt;, and it completely transformed the experience.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;The waterfalls were absolutely &lt;strong&gt;roaring&lt;/strong&gt; the most powerful I’ve ever seen them. The trail started out dry enough, but by the halfway point the skies opened and we got &lt;strong&gt;soaked&lt;/strong&gt;. Classic Yorkshire weather.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;A couple of changes on the route stood out:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;The once reliable &lt;strong&gt;ice-cream van is no longer there&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;However, there’s now a &lt;strong&gt;small kiosk&lt;/strong&gt; by the caravan park that does drinks and snacks, which was a welcome surprise.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;We got...</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>https://iczster.github.io/ingleton-falls-hike/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://iczster.github.io/ingleton-falls-hike/</guid>
        
        <category>hiking</category>
        
        <category>yorkshire</category>
        
        <category>waterfalls</category>
        
        <category>Hiking</category>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Hiking Whernside The Highest of the Yorkshire Three Peaks</title>
        <description>&lt;h3 id=&quot;️-hiking-to-the-top-of-whernside&quot;&gt;🏔️ Hiking to the Top of Whernside&lt;/h3&gt; &lt;p&gt;Whernside is the tallest of the &lt;strong&gt;Yorkshire Three Peaks&lt;/strong&gt;, and although it’s often called the gentler giant, the weather on this trip decided otherwise, still in the midst of a storm so we got lucky. We began at the mighty &lt;strong&gt;Ribblehead Viaduct&lt;/strong&gt;, an iconic and dramatic starting point.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Only a short way into the route, we reached a stunning &lt;strong&gt;waterfall section&lt;/strong&gt; a perfect early highlight before the long, steady ridge climb.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;hr /&gt; &lt;h3 id=&quot;️-a400-flyover-a-standout-moment&quot;&gt;✈️ A400 Flyover A Standout Moment&lt;/h3&gt; &lt;p&gt;Not long after passing the waterfall, a deep rumble echoed through the...</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>https://iczster.github.io/hiking-to-whernside-summit/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://iczster.github.io/hiking-to-whernside-summit/</guid>
        
        <category>hiking</category>
        
        <category>three-peaks</category>
        
        <category>yorkshire</category>
        
        <category>whernside</category>
        
        <category>summit</category>
        
        <category>Hiking</category>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Review: Fawlty Towers The Play Palace Theatre Manchester</title>
        <description>&lt;h2 id=&quot;review&quot;&gt;Review&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;p&gt;I managed to snag a couple of cheap tickets via Tickets and landed in the Palace Theatre for the touring production of &lt;em&gt;Fawlty Towers The Play&lt;/em&gt;. The evening is an affectionate, often uproarious stage distillation of John Cleese’s original sitcom. The production stitches together the best bits from three episodes into a tight two-hour farce, and the result mostly sings.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2 id=&quot;cast--performances&quot;&gt;Cast &amp;amp; performances&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;p&gt;The casting is the engine that powers this show. Danny Bayne’s Basil is all twitchy indignation and frantic physicality he clearly studies Cleese’s physical comedy and makes it his own. Mia Austen’s Sybil is...</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>https://iczster.github.io/fawlty-towers-review-palace-theatre/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://iczster.github.io/fawlty-towers-review-palace-theatre/</guid>
        
        <category>theatre</category>
        
        <category>palace</category>
        
        <category>play</category>
        
        <category>Theatre</category>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Gig Review: Tom Meighan @ Whittles, Oldham</title>
        <description>&lt;h3 id=&quot;review&quot;&gt;Review&lt;/h3&gt; &lt;p&gt;The small downstairs room at Whittles Tokyo Project in Oldham offered a modest, almost intimate setting for Tom Meighan’s return to the town. On a quiet Tuesday night, with only a modest turnout by his standards, the gig didn’t carry the energy of a large festival or arena show; instead it felt personal, lean and stripped-back.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;The evening opened with support from Aziz Ibrahim. His set, while uncertain in front of a sparse crowd, had some strong moments, a few standout guitar lines and a rawness in tone that hinted at what might be possible under fuller attendance....</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>https://iczster.github.io/tom-meighan-whittles-oldham/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://iczster.github.io/tom-meighan-whittles-oldham/</guid>
        
        <category>gig</category>
        
        <category>review</category>
        
        <category>music</category>
        
        <category>Music</category>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Review: Walk Right Back The Everly Brothers Story</title>
        <description>&lt;h3 id=&quot;walk-right-back-the-everly-brothers-story-theatre-royal-wakefield&quot;&gt;Walk Right Back The Everly Brothers Story Theatre Royal Wakefield&lt;/h3&gt; &lt;p&gt;I’m not entirely sure how I ended up at this show 🤷I was talked into going and I don’t have any particular interest in The Everly Brothers. Their music isn’t something I grew up with, and I couldn’t name more than one or two songs before stepping into the Theatre Royal Wakefield. So expectations were modest at best.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;To my surprise, &lt;em&gt;Walk Right Back&lt;/em&gt; turned out to be an enjoyable night. It’s a brisk, good-natured tribute musical that rattles through the Everly Brothers’ story with a mix of live...</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>https://iczster.github.io/walk-right-back-everly-brothers/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://iczster.github.io/walk-right-back-everly-brothers/</guid>
        
        <category>theatre</category>
        
        <category>tribute</category>
        
        <category>music</category>
        
        <category>Theatre</category>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Building My Own Blog Site with Jekyll</title>
        <description>&lt;h2 id=&quot;why-i-chose-jekyll-for-my-blog&quot;&gt;Why I Chose Jekyll for My Blog&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;p&gt;Creating your own blog gives you &lt;strong&gt;full control&lt;/strong&gt; over content, design, and performance. I wanted a platform that:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;Is lightweight and fast ✅&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Supports &lt;strong&gt;Markdown&lt;/strong&gt; content naturally 📄&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Allows &lt;strong&gt;full customization&lt;/strong&gt; without relying on WordPress or hosted platforms 🎨&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Integrates easily with &lt;strong&gt;GitHub Pages&lt;/strong&gt; for free hosting 🌐&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Can showcase my interests: &lt;strong&gt;film, tech, hiking, sport, and music&lt;/strong&gt; 🎬🚀🏞️⚽🎵&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;p&gt;Jekyll is perfect because it’s a &lt;strong&gt;static site generator&lt;/strong&gt; that converts Markdown posts into a fast, responsive website. Paired with the &lt;strong&gt;Jekflix theme&lt;/strong&gt;, I can create a cinematic, modern design tailored...</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>https://iczster.github.io/building-my-own-blog-site-with-jekyll/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://iczster.github.io/building-my-own-blog-site-with-jekyll/</guid>
        
        <category>tech</category>
        
        <category>blogging</category>
        
        <category>tutorial</category>
        
        <category>jekyll</category>
        
        <category>Tech</category>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Review: Young Frankenstein @ Hope Mill Theatre</title>
        <description>&lt;h2 id=&quot;young-frankenstein--hope-mill-theatre-what-a-night&quot;&gt;Young Frankenstein @ Hope Mill Theatre what a night&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;p&gt;I went into &lt;em&gt;Young Frankenstein&lt;/em&gt; with high hopes I’ve always loved the original film and I was curious to see how it would translate to the stage in a smaller venue. A pre-show pizza and drink at the Hope Mill Theatre set the tone perfectly. It’s a fantastic little theatre: tucked away, quirky, relaxed, and with the sort of atmosphere that makes you feel part of the night before anything even starts.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;What unfolded on stage was one of the most entertaining theatre experiences I’ve had in a while slapstick,...</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>https://iczster.github.io/young-frankenstein/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://iczster.github.io/young-frankenstein/</guid>
        
        <category>theatre</category>
        
        <category>musical</category>
        
        <category>comedy</category>
        
        <category>Theatre</category>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Review: New Dawn Fades @ The Met, Bury</title>
        <description>&lt;h2 id=&quot;new-dawn-fades--the-met-bury&quot;&gt;New Dawn Fades @ The Met, Bury&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;p&gt;As a massive Joy Division fan, &lt;em&gt;New Dawn Fades&lt;/em&gt; was an irresistible proposition. Not just a retelling of the band’s story, but staged in &lt;strong&gt;the very room&lt;/strong&gt; that witnessed one of its most chaotic moments the infamous 1979 gig that descended into a riot and has now entered Mancunian folklore.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;The Met is a fantastic little theatre: small, intimate, and atmospheric, yet relaxed and welcoming. It has a bar and seating area for pre-show drinks, a small museum and shop connected to the production, and is run by passionate volunteers. That combination...</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>https://iczster.github.io/new-dawn-fades/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://iczster.github.io/new-dawn-fades/</guid>
        
        <category>theatre</category>
        
        <category>drama</category>
        
        <category>music</category>
        
        <category>joy-division</category>
        
        <category>bury-met</category>
        
        <category>Theatre</category>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Review: The Story of The Kinks @ Palace Theatre Manchester</title>
        <description>&lt;h2 id=&quot;the-story-of-the-kinks--palace-theatre-manchester&quot;&gt;The Story of The Kinks @ Palace Theatre Manchester&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;p&gt;I’ll admit: I’m &lt;strong&gt;not a big fan&lt;/strong&gt; of The Kinks. When it was &lt;del&gt;suggested&lt;/del&gt; told catching &lt;em&gt;The Story of The Kinks&lt;/em&gt; at Palace Theatre, I was tired, skeptical, and half ready to bail. Somehow, despite the grogginess and lack of enthusiasm I ended up buying a ticket. And I’m genuinely glad I did.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h3 id=&quot;-what-the-show-is&quot;&gt;🎭 What the show is&lt;/h3&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Story of The Kinks&lt;/em&gt; blends biography with live performance. It charts the band’s journey from their roots in 1960s London, through their chart‑topping hits, internal tensions, artistic reinventions, and cultural...</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>https://iczster.github.io/the-story-of-the-kinks/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://iczster.github.io/the-story-of-the-kinks/</guid>
        
        <category>theatre</category>
        
        <category>music</category>
        
        <category>tribute</category>
        
        <category>Theatre</category>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Skiddaw Summit via Jenkins Bridleway</title>
        <description>&lt;h2 id=&quot;hiking-to-skiddaw-summit--little-man&quot;&gt;Hiking to Skiddaw Summit &amp;amp; Little Man&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Overview&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Parking isnt great and you need to arrive early to have any chance of a parking space (the car park is small). Otherwise this was a fantastic hike with great views. We even managed to experience a cloud inversion.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;After some early clag this cleared and its a pretty steep and brutal ascent. We took in Skiddaw little man also and recommend you tackle this afer summitting.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h3 id=&quot;key-hike-points&quot;&gt;Key Hike Points&lt;/h3&gt; &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;Steep but rewarding ascent&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Cloud inversion at the summit&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Claggy start&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Limited parking (arrive early)&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;h3 id=&quot;quote-from-the-hike&quot;&gt;Quote from...</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 19:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>https://iczster.github.io/hiking-skiddaw-via-jenkinshill/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://iczster.github.io/hiking-skiddaw-via-jenkinshill/</guid>
        
        <category>hiking</category>
        
        <category>summit</category>
        
        <category>lakes</category>
        
        <category>Hiking</category>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Review: First Light @ Shaw Playhouse</title>
        <description>&lt;h3 id=&quot;first-light--shaw-playhouse&quot;&gt;First Light @ Shaw Playhouse&lt;/h3&gt; &lt;p&gt;As someone wit#h a real interest in history and having studied the First World War in some depth I was genuinely looking forward to &lt;em&gt;First Light&lt;/em&gt;. The premise alone was enough to intrigue me: a play exploring the human cost of war beyond the battlefield, grappling with guilt, duty, and the forgotten stories of ordinary men. This was also poignant with them being from around the Manchester area.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Thankfully, the production delivered something that felt emotionally resonant and intellectually engaging.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h3 id=&quot;-what-is-the-play-about&quot;&gt;🎭 What is the play about&lt;/h3&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;First Light&lt;/em&gt; written by Mark Hayhurst and...</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>https://iczster.github.io/first-light/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://iczster.github.io/first-light/</guid>
        
        <category>theatre</category>
        
        <category>drama</category>
        
        <category>war</category>
        
        <category>review</category>
        
        <category>Theatre</category>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Creating a Reusable Hike Info Box in Jekyll</title>
        <description>&lt;h2 id=&quot;introduction&quot;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;p&gt;In this post, I’ll explain how I created a &lt;strong&gt;reusable Hike Info Box&lt;/strong&gt; for my hiking posts using &lt;strong&gt;Jekyll and the Jekflix theme&lt;/strong&gt;. The system is modular and can be adapted to &lt;strong&gt;any category&lt;/strong&gt;, whether hiking, tech tutorials, recipes, or music albums.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;The main goals:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;ol&gt; &lt;li&gt;Store metadata in the &lt;strong&gt;front-matter&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Render a visually appealing info box with &lt;strong&gt;icons, animations, and badges&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Only display the box for relevant posts.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Make it &lt;strong&gt;easy to reuse for future posts&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ol&gt; &lt;hr /&gt; &lt;h2 id=&quot;step-1-add-metadata-to-post-front-matter&quot;&gt;Step 1: Add Metadata to Post Front-Matter&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;p&gt;Jekyll posts allow &lt;strong&gt;custom variables&lt;/strong&gt; in the YAML front-matter. For...</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 11:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>https://iczster.github.io/creating-hikebox-tutorial/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://iczster.github.io/creating-hikebox-tutorial/</guid>
        
        <category>tech</category>
        
        <category>blog</category>
        
        <category>jekyll</category>
        
        <category>tutorial</category>
        
        <category>Tech</category>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Trip Review: Neuschwanstein &amp; Hohenschwangau Castles A Day Out from Munich</title>
        <description>&lt;h3 id=&quot;a-day-trip-to-neuschwanstein--hohenschwangau-our-munich-getaway-treat&quot;&gt;A day trip to Neuschwanstein &amp;amp; Hohenschwangau our Munich get‑away treat&lt;/h3&gt; &lt;p&gt;We booked the day trip through a tour platform (GetYourGuide), and from the very start everything ran smoothly: pick up from central Munich was on time, and the coach was comfortable enough for the 2‑ish hour ride. I grabbed a coffee and a croissant before boarding a simple start that became part of the vibe for the day: relaxed but excited.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h3 id=&quot;️-timeline--itinerary&quot;&gt;🗓️ Timeline / Itinerary&lt;/h3&gt; &lt;table&gt; &lt;thead&gt; &lt;tr&gt; &lt;th&gt;Time&lt;/th&gt; &lt;th&gt;Activity&lt;/th&gt; &lt;th&gt;Notes&lt;/th&gt; &lt;/tr&gt; &lt;/thead&gt; &lt;tbody&gt; &lt;tr&gt; &lt;td&gt;08:00&lt;/td&gt; &lt;td&gt;Pick up in Munich&lt;/td&gt; &lt;td&gt;Comfortable coach ride, coffee &amp;amp; croissant in...</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>https://iczster.github.io/neuschwanstein-munich-castle/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://iczster.github.io/neuschwanstein-munich-castle/</guid>
        
        <category>travel</category>
        
        <category>Munich</category>
        
        <category>Neuschwanstein</category>
        
        <category>Travel</category>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>What&apos;s the difference between Observability &amp; Monitoring?</title>
        <description>&lt;h2 id=&quot;introduction&quot;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;p&gt;I often get asked what is the difference between observability and monitoring and should observability replace monitoring? Lets take it back to the premise of what traditional monitoring is. This is my first article in my &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;Site Reliability Engineering&lt;/code&gt; series.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;I have been involved in monitoring over 20 years and the design, architecture and implementation of a whole range of monitoring tools across both open source and enterprise.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Monitoring is about the &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;known knowns&lt;/code&gt; and traditionally this would involve the templating up of these scenarios and coding them into the monitoring stack for infrastructure...</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 29 Mar 2022 11:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>https://iczster.github.io/what-is-the-difference-between-observability-and-monitoring/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://iczster.github.io/what-is-the-difference-between-observability-and-monitoring/</guid>
        
        <category>tech</category>
        
        <category>blog</category>
        
        <category>SRE</category>
        
        <category>observability</category>
        
        <category>Tech</category>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Beginners Guide to building in GCP with Terraform</title>
        <description>&lt;h2 id=&quot;goal&quot;&gt;Goal&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;p&gt;This article will set out what you need in order to be able to standup an automated build of a VM (Google Cloud) a web server (Apache) and Ansible.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h3 id=&quot;what-will-we-cover&quot;&gt;What will we cover&lt;/h3&gt; &lt;p&gt;Deployment of a Google Compute VM instance using Terraform Use of a Compute Instance startup script or user-data Rendering a Terraform template Dependencies&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;You have created a GCP account (or trial account). You will receive $300 of credits and also 750 hours per month will be free if you select the e2-micro instance. More information can be found in the tutorial below including the...</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Mar 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>https://iczster.github.io/beginners-guide-to-building-in-gcp-with-terraform/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://iczster.github.io/beginners-guide-to-building-in-gcp-with-terraform/</guid>
        
        <category>tech</category>
        
        <category>blog</category>
        
        <category>GCP</category>
        
        <category>tutorial</category>
        
        <category>Tech</category>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
